<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Adrián Cidre</title>
<link>https://cidree.github.io/blog/projects.html</link>
<atom:link href="https://cidree.github.io/blog/projects.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description></description>
<generator>quarto-1.4.193</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 22:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>Presentation</title>
  <dc:creator>Adrián Cidre</dc:creator>
  <link>https://cidree.github.io/blog/posts/000-Presentation/index.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<blockquote class="blockquote">
<h1 id="introducing-myself">Introducing myself</h1>
</blockquote>
<p>My name is Adrián Cidre González, and I hold a degree in Forestry Engineering from the University of Santiago de Compostela. Currently, I am pursuing my master’s degree in Geomatics, Remote Sensing, and Spatial Models applied to Forest Management at the University of Córdoba (Spain).</p>
<p>Not only am I a dedicated student, but I am also actively involved in practical research. I am currently working as a research assistant in the LIFE-FAGESOS project at the University of Córdoba. This project allows me to contribute to cutting-edge work related to forest management, protection and sustainability.</p>
<p>Within the scope of my research, I specialize in data analysis, specifically as a data analyst. One of my primary responsibilities involves creating models of pests in Europe for the LIFE-PROJECT that I am currently engaged in. Using my skills in the R environment, I perform spatial data analysis and modeling, as well as remote sensing analysis.</p>
<p>In addition to my academic pursuits and research, I am excited to use this blog as a platform to share my work, courses, and other fascinating topics that will engage and inform the public. By providing valuable insights into my field and showcasing the projects I am involved in, I aim to spark interest and foster a greater understanding of the importance of forestry, geomatics, and data analysis in sustainable forest management.</p>



 ]]></description>
  <category>personal</category>
  <guid>https://cidree.github.io/blog/posts/000-Presentation/index.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://cidree.github.io/blog/posts/000-Presentation/image.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
